import Question from '@/types/question';

export const questions: Question[] = [
  {
    question: 'What is the decimal equivalent of the binary number 1010?',
    options: ['2', '5', '10', '15'],
    answers: ['C'],
  },
  {
    question: 'In the octal numbering system, what is the value of 14)10?',
    options: ['12', '14', '16', '20'],
    answers: ['A'],
  },
  {
    question:
      'What is the hexadecimal representation of the decimal number 255?',
    options: ['FF', 'FE', '2F', '1E'],
    answers: ['A'],
  },
  {
    question: 'What is 90065)10 in decimal representation?',
    options: ['90201', '90065', '90543', '90876'],
    answers: ['B'],
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the decimal equivalent of the binary number 1011010?',
    options: ['94', '92', '96', '90'],
    answers: ['D'],
  },
  {
    question:
      'If the number 3431 is in base 5, what is the decimal equivalent?',
    options: ['491', '521', '553', '587'],
    answers: ['A'],
  },
  {
    question: 'Convert the following hexadecimal number to binary: 182E',
    options: [
      '1 1000 0010 1110',
      '1 1010 0010 1110',
      '1 1100 0010 1110',
      '1 1110 0010 1110',
    ],
    answers: ['A'],
  },
  {
    question: 'Convert the following hexadecimal number to binary: C362',
    options: [
      '1100 0011 0100 0010',
      '1100 0011 0110 0010',
      '1100 0011 0010 0010',
      '1100 0011 0001 0010',
    ],
    answers: ['B'],
  },
  {
    question:
      'Convert the following binary number to hexadecimal: 1111 0011 0001',
    options: ['F31', 'E23', 'D15', 'C07'],
    answers: ['A'],
  },
  {
    question:
      'Convert the following binary number to hexadecimal: 100 0101 0110 1101',
    options: ['476F', '465E', '456D', '4870'],
    answers: ['C'],
  },
];
